I'm going to interrupt, I'll also bring your
client in. We're in class number 4,
and it's called Charter
Phone Research, chapter 5,
The Elements. Okay, we're
investigating the elements, the five
elements. This version includes
space.
I'm spending a lot of money. Let's see
the rest. A $20 question:
Why do you think I chose space?
A $10 fight: Who is
correct?
[Laughter]
I think it's because it's difficult. It's
the most complicated to understand. This is worth
three dollars.
And because if we can understand the emptiness
of space, then we'll be able to
understand the nature of space.
Then we'll realize that
space isn't changing. $12. Do you
want to add something? You can do it
together.
[Music]
And understand the definition of space, and
so we'll be able to understand that space
is empty. Okay, you've reached 1995.
There's one more thing I need
about the emptiness of space. So
we can understand the emptiness of other things.
That's fine.
Two dollars.
Where are you in the caste?
Space is an object that is
defined by the absence of things.
normally defined by the absence of
things. So the  Space has its
own gas, which is a waste of space.
Space is something physical.
If you can see the flow of
Nagarjuna's wisdom, they are very
good people. If it doesn't seem like they are just
random topics, that they don't seem
connected to each other, but if you can
understand the flow of the chapters,
then you are really beginning to
understand the arguments. There is a flow in
the competition with the last chapter. In the
last one, we talked about the physical body and
all those molecules and atoms,
and now we are moving to space
because the definition of space is the
absence of camps of something concrete. It is
frequently used to describe
emptiness. Space is empty of something
that actually exists. If it is something physical,
like these amazing
signs we make, if it's a
very famous center, they're going to charge you
$200 for something like this, but you can probably
get something for $5.
Let's say $10. I think $10
for your house. Some explanation, but you
put it on your doorstep while you're meditating,
and you hope someone will notice it anyway.
The space where
this sign is is occupying
some space.
That space is empty.
If emptiness is in our great emptiness...
So this would be pushed out, so there's
empty space, and this, what's it
called, is a sign, a meditation sign,
and it's occupying that space. It does
n't have a physical form
because otherwise the sign would be
pushed out, but it's empty, it exists, it exists.
But space is what
gives things their place, space so they can
be. Some people define
space as the distance between the
microphone and the mouth, which people
say is the element of space
here. That's their definition of
space, but that's not
Buddhist space. Buddhist space means
where things are placed,
empty chairs, and something sits there, but
the chair stays empty.
If someone gets up, then it's
very similar to emptiness.
Space is very popular, a very
popular theme in Buddhism because there's a
hook, there's something that isn't there, and that
allows other things to be there. Do you
understand? Of course, it's
moving into space because it's the
most difficult, most complicated element,
but it's also
very similar to emptiness. There's
a gas, there's something missing. Do
you understand? It's a
mental problem, so the
humor...  It focuses on space, and many
of the meditations are named after
space, which means you
have to think about the emptiness of
things, or you can call them
spaced out.
And I like that you've studied the four
steps of meditation. I mean, we don't have
time to do it this week; it's very
complicated, but it's at level 17, and
you can do the four different
spaces. It's very useful. It's a very useful idea.
This letter, what's the captcha in the
kitchen?
[Music]
The husband, I didn't do anything. Is he
there?
No, no, he's not. It's impossible.
It would seem that he's there. If that's
called ignorance, it's the first link. Your
change can teach you
the Wheel of Life. I hope that you
can teach it in Bali. That would be very
good. It goes deeper and deeper, like, you're getting
deeper. You make a good team. So you're
going to explain the Wheel of
Life.
[Music]
In the chapter that's trying to
prepare our minds for the idea of
capturing something that's missing, something that
's defined by something that's absent,
something that's lacking.
Where is it in the human computer?
I have to judge if they know this or not.
that be perfect
because you have to be perfect
definition of space
the exact exact and traditional
exact words there are 4
if I have to pay 2 534 wrong
I want the definition of space from the
scriptures
is the division of the definition of
scattering means the things
you can touch are the things you can
touch
the man from Shanghai to him it is said he you cannot
touch him they do not
touch and they say because his wisdom
cuts through things like a
hot knife through butter
so the name of Shanghai
means like an extremely
sharp knife that only you if you cut
things
his name is no touch touch you read
now in the definition of space is to
say anything that can that
can block you something physical
simply absences not only is not there that it is not can that cannot stop you cannot stop you cannot have it
is open is free you
can move in it is the definition of
space about digan
frei means to touch and all means to hit touch hit to shoot stop them to stop to give to
stop and
hit
touch stop is just the definition of
space has been looking for a man
for me I
think that  It's going to be a very good name,
what was I saying, let it play for me
alone, I
think it's going to be very possible, maybe not, of
course, I don't have a band because a
musical group because one of the
members had a baby, I hope
you are well, Eren and Nick,
well now it's
a phrase, it has words to play,
sorry, hit, play, stop, it's just
the tradition of Quispe, traditional,
I like to say empty space because it does
n't mean outside of space, you don't
want to go where you fly, where
rockets are launched to the other side of the moon,
that's not that space, it's a space here,
the zoo, sometimes I like to call it
empty space, even the definition is that,
and we started talking about that
yesterday
about the definition, the definition, the
definition from the definition, because in
Buddhism, especially Nagarjuna, we are
very precise about our decisions,
our decisions, and he is precise in his
definitions, so you're going to have fewer
arguments against business if
everything is clear, if it's
totally active, how do you define
a trip to teach in another country,
in Romania, how do you define that,
how many days exactly, who is
seeing, who was taking care of the children,
who is going to pay for that, this is the
Definition of a trip to Romania
and if you, your life will be much easier
if you define things clearly in your
life and in your marriage.
Wood is very clear
and it was and I'm going to share them
from Adam's text.
We're going to talk about the definition of a
definition.
The definition of a definition, whether you
want to be substantial, something
physical, real, something with substance, like,
how many days exactly in Romania
and exactly how much money it's going to
cost us.
That attitude, we want that attitude.
She means both her stay and
things. This refers to
this, which means it's ceramics and
clay, or ceramics that you're surfing. It's as
real as this house, something with substance.
The word with substance means
clay, porcelain. The person in a second
link of life is that,
is a potter. I mean a
Saturn,
a person in the SAP business. I mean,
I'm a real foreigner. With
substance, fusion, are moments, uses, water. I
mean, the dictionary, to
give it to you for free.
Three qualities have to be
present for something to be a
definition. The definition has to have
three different things for it to be a
definition, and those must
be substantial. Here we go, which ones?  It's
three o'clock, don't remember that, that's
a definition.
Generally speaking, it has
three qualities and three requirements.
The first one has to
sound like a definition.
Generally, someone has to be saying, "
This is the definition." It's a definition. It
probably has to have
some words that describe that thing.
Right, it
should sound like a definition. The
definition of a good lunch is something that is
called... that you like.
Secondly, rankings in the meter system.
With the correct position, the person
can see that it applies to what they are
defining. If hot and burn, that's
the definition of fire.
So the second requirement for making
a good definition is that fire
must have heat and burn.
The pieces that we expect in a
decrease must apply to the thing you
are defining. So
listen, it's heat and burn. That's a good definition of fire.
If it's
heat and burn and always frozen, that's
a good definition of fire.
Because the third one... no, reader,
the shovel doesn't fit the first one. So,
first, it has to sound like a
definition. It has to have pieces, parts,
and without certain qualities
of fire: it's heat, it's always
frozen.
The first quality is this, and the second one
is there because... because always  Frozen does
n't apply, fire
suffers, so so far two of the
third qualities, the definition of a
definition, the definition of a
definition, the first must have a
list of qualities:
hot burns and always has, and
frozen sounds like a definition without a
number. 2
All three qualities I
talked about apply to fire, no, so it
means if it's the thing you're
defining, it's also called dirty, what
you're defining
in logic, but you can say the thing we're
defining in chapter 5,
mainly the space
in which the third part of the
Mitchell definition
in sessions should
n't be left as a definition of
anything, nothing added to anything else, it can't be
left as a definition of anything else.
The definition of a Toyota is any
vehicle with four wheels, the
definition of a Toyota is any
vehicle with four wheels, good
definition, no, because
other things also fit, the
favors also fit, the Chevrolets, the Subarus,
so the definition must be that
difficult, the definition of that should
be specific to that game, did you
understand,
father?
Those three requirements of the definition
must be a definition, the parts
must fit perfectly, and the
definition cannot  To be a little more
like in the forums in the chalets,
those three requirements are easy, they're
easy, anyone can say that if it's
the first part of the definition
that wants to be substantial,
constant, it means that something about
the definition must be substantial,
and it's easier to understand what is
substantial if we try to understand what is
not substance, not what has no
substance
will be unique. She always makes me enchiladas
when you come over, unless you do it, no, I
'm not suggesting, I'm also
saying I had a chile relleno last
night from a certain person, it was
incredible, I was in
chile relleno paradise for like an hour,
and I'm going to make you some enchiladas
when she arrives. I say yes please,
for your band, your spiritual advancement, they're going
to see her Friday,
but sometimes she's busy because her mom is
n't well, maybe she has to go to the
end first, they can't, so
enchiladas, nothing more, it became
just a name, the name is enchiladas, it
's not just a name, I do
n't know why
the grape
25 because I had to help her so that the
web could make money.
[Music]
is a good idea, but it's a
future thing that will never  Something in the future is going to happen
that will never happen, not even in
Chillã da. If Veronica isn't angry, she's
not well, so she's going to go see
movies. So I'm never going to have a
Chilaba enchilada. It's called tact. Say it's
only in words, it's called
enchiladas, it
has no substance, no substance.
When they come here, well, it's going to be
a delicious enchilada. I'll eat it, Edson.
According to that, it does have substance. She talks
about the enchilada. Her mom is
sick, so she never arrives. So it's
only ice cream in name, and we're not
talking about just one name, coffee. The
definition
of the thing you're defining is
only the name, the acted-up enchilada, which is
never going to happen.
You must be confused. You're confused. I
hope you're confused.
The definition of something, to give a
definition
that isn't real, isn't substantial, is
only an idea, is only a picture,
is a photograph of the enchilada. It's about
eating a picture of a
rented enchilada, and finally you're going to lose
weight
because you don't have any calories.
So the fire has to be
only the real name, it's substantial.
About Buddhist
medical traditions in the US, we talk  The other day they're
like sentences from a bad boyfriend, he
never puts his arm around you
when you want a hug. That's the
similar definition, which is a sentence.
Sentences look like words, but
Buddhism is high, it's the opposite, it's the other way around.
The real thing is how hot it is, it touches you and
burns your fingers. That's the
real thing, or the definition is real.
But what is the definition of fire?
To play,
by your statement, how do you say to be
quiet, to
peel wool?
When a big fire is called "fail"
in Russian,
that's just one word.
Please don't, because it's very hot.
The thing you're defining in Buddhism
is just one word,
and the definition is essentially heat that
burns your finger. We normally think of
the definition as a sentence. If
we think that the definition is just
bad, well, in Buddhism it's the other way around. What it means is
that in
Buddhism the definition, the
real thing, is heat.
Their words in Sanskrit
for this task is the action: '
l á s h y n a 6 s h m
in the zone.'
[Music]
Roxana has two meanings. The wave acts
has two meanings.
The first is definition,
it's a sign, an indication, and  A sign,
an indication, like you know your husband
is angry. Well, you get a
red mark on his face.
The color red is a sign that he's
upset. It's a sign, like
a sign: "Annoyed husband." With reds, it
's interesting to understand that
the sign of the red face... well,
husband, be the word to
define it. In the sweet, they will
bring it,
and definition is the same in Buddhism.
In the sign, and to define, it's a definition, it's
the same word: hybridity. Anything
that has these two dreams: heat
and that burns your finger will satisfy those
games.
That's game. In fact, the name for
definition in Buddhism is signs, signals,
fire signs, courage, and that kills, burns your
fingers.
Now listen, if someone tells you that it's
an act of failing in class, they say, "
Tomorrow, if you took half an hour to
think, but you remembered the
word, you said, 'But it can't happen,'
and you said, 'Can you explain to me what it is?'
Now, at that moment, you
also think that it's something. At that
moment, if you don't know, you use what you imagine it is. It's like
something worthwhile to me. It's
like jelly without  Defining my voice that
seeks me went to you, so
maybe your tests are more
interesting now. Think of
the words, and someone is the oldest, and you are
like these people who refuse.
Everyone is under different pressure. It must
be something, it must be a thing.
What is the account? What is the picture in your
mind of that thing? For me, it's like
ordinary gelatin. It's like
something, I don't know, like a piece of
gelatin.
It's something, but I don't know what it is. It's just a
thing for me. It's like before you
define it for me, but I know it's something. I already know something. I do
n't know. It looks like gelatin. It's a
dessert I used to get because it's cheap, and we
have four children without parents.
But it's like a fish from before I could get
home. I don't know what you're
talking about, but I don't know exactly
what it is. I don't understand what it is. So what
happens is that it has it and
tells you something hot and burning, tax pressure.
Suddenly, then Bayern became more
real,
like on the stove, like in a cigarette.
The mental image changes. Before, it was like
transparent gelatin,
and then someone told me hot and
burning. So the
mental image transformed into...  It was made in a kind of fire,
something like fire,
but normally in the stove or something.
So the thing that's going to be defined
was, did it have substance, or was it just... I
only had a name.
Info before I tell you the
characteristics, before I ask for
the characteristics, the
substantial, the
substantial characteristics. So
what you're defining
is just a something, and then I
convince you of the characteristics, or
characteristics about extensions. It's going
to burn your finger, almost, and if you get
close and it starts to feel hotter and hotter,
soon the image makes the question that
now I have to stop the class
at 10:30.
I guarantee that we're going to take a
bathroom break. What was I
talking about? So here it is, here's
the important thing of the chapter.
Before, the fire or the definition?
Oh,
both. That wasn't my question. You're
talking to your opponent who came
first.
Beautiful, but don't tell the joke until
I'm ready.
And then, because you put the definition, there's no
thing, there's no place where the
definition goes. Even if you describe it, the
definition must rest on the thing.
Ashton, the heat and what burns, there has to
be something, there has to be a... and
There has to be something there, a
master commerce plan on the blog. It has to
be first. It ca
n't be because it can't be
burning hot until people have the
definition. So there's no fire.
How do you know that heat has to be the
topic before what you're saying came
first, right, user? And then say, I'm going to do it.
Nobody cares about being a
definition of something that is so hot
that it contributes to me because I've
observed fire. You can't make a
definition
unless the people are there
inside. But it can't be fire until it's hot, until it has
a definition
so that it's hot. There can't
be a correct game
of what is hot, well, fire
until it has the heat. And what to
curse after you have the definition.
Which came first, the fire or the heat? And
what else is all I'm
asking? And tell me, and then I could go to the
bathroom. Which came first?
And now I say more,
and both are wrong.
First the fire. There was
a fire that after this
we decided to give a definition that it
was hot, that it burns. Which of the two
came first? Well, it
follows lies about a
few more minutes.
There are four factors in
concerted Buddhism, four
basic things, things, I was saying, level  7 reach
force one 55 things the factors I'm
going to teach you someday but that's
called what forces you to have to
trigger
perception don't see the rate in my hand
I had to hold the
white chain and the personification in your mind I know
very well chapter 3
chapter 3 that the rate of change the
cells of the then the rate was
first
if he wants you to do is that you
do this something strange
first
l  At the expert rate, the eye
was already there.
What is happening? What is going on in
signing cancer? If you are not confused,
then you don't understand. To the face,
if you are not confused, you don't understand. It is
confused. Where does the fire come from?
Where does the blue come from? Where did the eye come from? The
rate and the madman, the eyeball
came from a karmic seed. The rate
and the madman,
although the eye came from the rate, the rate
of the logo, bad question because then
make coffee for other people,
not just the one to check. The
goal is to help other people. It does
n't reach people, so they are
studying emptiness and they didn't understand
the terminal logic. Therefore,
you should have served coffee to
someone else. Therefore, you have to
share. If there are people who don't
get food in the world, then you
must share your food. Therefore, there is
always a. Therefore, therefore,
you must feed the people in
Africa. You can't because that is where
the rate comes from, and it wasn't that the madman
was before the little cup. First,
because the fire was lit, the
burning was first. It is what we are saying that
other people who need
logic have to go without physical care,
affecting  A button to see if that's
enough. It's going to end with everyone. You do
n't have to think about other people
because that's denial. To the abdomen, take
a break, go to the bathroom
in about 15 more minutes. He's
doing this. It's a counter. It's
like this boring nerd from Avid Arma
and keeps pulling things out. But basic
Buddhist teachings, basic physical ones, the first
chapter of life, which is called
the three themes, are
we talking about the parts of the
person, we're talking about the 18
parts of reality, and we're talking
about the sensory organs. It's
mainly very famous themes in
the Book of Life. It's
the first bible,
it's like his great book.
These are the first things that the Buddha
said must exist from your own
side. It's the first thing they're going to teach you,
something that isn't there,
especially the first talk. These
people, Vancouver James,
to
the people who are now real
because they're going to Vancouver to talk about
their success stories,
the first thing you say is you have to
look smart, dress well,
lies, lies. The second or
third time, but the first time you have to
make a very good impression.
The first teaching of Mr. Wood,
waiting.  149 days before I teach, I
was probably lost
buying my suit,
and the first thing is the first thing I have to
say because I wanted everyone to see how
smart they are. So the
first thing they're going to say in Vancouver is that they
have to say something wonderful in
a new city.
3, 4, and 5,
then maybe on the ninth or tenth
time I went, the day was over.
Something core, I say something crazy, but not
in the first one. In the first one, I'm going to say
something good. I want people to come back.
Another thing, all the topics I
talked about, and it has a Wi-Fi connection that is
natural and doesn't come from me. It doesn't come from me.
And for each of those three other
chapters, 3, 4, and 5, they're talking about the
connection,
Nacho, that is natural. Nobody made it. It's
an expression of my seed. It's
just natural.
That's how things are. Charter eggs.
What was the topic of chapter 3 about? The eye. The eye
sees things. Nobody. Nobody made that. So you ca
n't have a world where when you
see this, this horrible dark green drink,
there's a connection between the red and the
green. Nobody made that.
The work of the  The eye is the color of
colors, that's what we do.
Colors are what the eyes' job
is to see colors. Nobody did it
without having green. Well, you can have
orange or brown,
that's natural.
It's a connection between my coffee, the
color brown, and my eye. It's natural. Chapter
4: What follows:
Go to the atoms, go to the atoms. It
has some elements, and each molecule
has things that can be touched, smelled, and
felt. Especially that's it. It didn't
get up in the morning, it's night. Surely we have
something that works, that wakes up,
more so that they work. I have
complaints. I have to take out my
element of heat to be able to have a
warm coffee. Nobody did that. These
connections are natural. What is the
third one in Chapter 5?
It's by the Laksana room,
but what is the old message, signs
Miranda Garcia? When you get up to make
coffee in the morning, you don't
have to put the heat to the fire, you don't
have to extend the heat to the
box of the scheme and take something out and things,
detach the lime in the stove so that you can
lime the coffee is natural, and
the fire is the gas, and then, then  You look
for where the heat source is and you take
some heat, you find the container of what
burns and you put it on the gas and
then it catches fire, it's
automatic, here you understand, it's the
action. Because action has
two meanings, the first is the
definition that people use, putting
doors of love, but there is also
something more intimate, a more intimate reader, that is,
hot, which belongs to the body, it is
always connected with fire, the
root of the
word, action, which you are going to put in
your homework, is the axis, and I mean
connected, something attached to something else, it
means attached,
from Sahagún, they are
[Music]
we need a word
in Russian, it is
attached, this means attached, if it
comes from the same root,
by the way, if you want the reason why you have to
do your homework, you can say, milk
is a word, it is a special sound that
lives in hot water, and when you
stand in hot water,
the connector connects, it likes to
connect to your skin and it is difficult to
remove it, it is difficult to tear it off,
and so the
word
means animal with reader that
connects with
the indefinite, but it also wants
Saying design heat and burns, think about it, they're
stuck all the time, they've been
stuck to the fire all the
time, they're
always stuck to the fire. It
means that from the group of people
who want to fight for the
Roman Empire, he comes from the same root.
So look,
and he put the action on Lenin, he put the
signs in the fire, it's always like that.
So the word
that makes you feel natural, that you
have self-existence naturally,
nobody did it, not from the beginning.
The fire, we're always
hot, nobody put the heat in the fire.
Who said that, that is,
with the correct accent,
and nobody put the heat in the fire. Look, he
wants to destroy the research.
You are the one we are investigating in
this chapter. Who are we
investigating?
That question, the question to whoever
in the world
is a pill you take, it takes away the headache. It's
the definition of action, it's
a definition, and it's also a part.
It's what flexion does, what
aspirin does. Do you understand,
chapter 3, problems with the color orange and
the eye,
that connection isn't automatic. They're a
little far away. Maybe you're right about the
bodies they didn't create. Well, you get
closer and closer, you do 18, and then it makes you fat.
There  Some connection you don't like,
that's the next chapter we're going to talk
about not-so-close connections.
Who can divide the heat of the fire?
Who can say the heat isn't for the
fire, isn't part of the fire? He's
talking about the natural connection.
Natural connections
are like an aspirin connected to eliminate your
headache. I'm
not going to say, listen, the important thing is that it's
an aspirin connected to take away your
headache.
Half of the aspirins don't work. Haven't you
noticed that they didn't bother me? It bothers me. That's when
your mom
tells you, do you remember that moment? I
remember very well. Okay, even where I was. I was
in my brother's room
because I wasn't vomiting.
Two hours later I told her, "Sometimes it doesn't
work." And I was like, I would have asked her
what the
definition is, but I said, "Because Mom is
God. The
stars don't work all the
time, but
fixing your head is
the definition of natural connections."
What's the sign that the action of
aspirin isn't natural?
It's an aspirin that doesn't have the action. It does
n't feel strange.
You think it's coming from somewhere else. Maybe you
have to do something different
for it to work. For the
aspirins to work, you have to help.  to someone else
to take away their headache,
you understand who's talking to a
letter, you don't notice that something, the spas
sometimes don't work, where you've been the
last 20 or 50 years, it's
the sign of aspirin, they're
not connected to their objects
naturally, who connects us with whom,
his good bank deeds always
return to good deeds, when am I going to
stop there because we don't have time,
but it's fun,
we have time, what Jong-il loves
every chapter is that he goes to his trachea,
endure this, and if we have time it would be
something very nice, like as a dessert of
each chapter we could have, like me,
a churro
[Music]
people think that sometimes I'm
suggesting churros, maybe he told me no no no no don't
say that because there are people who
disappear and go to buy
churros, but I'm not saying other
kinds, I'm just joking,
ends the chapter, referring to
a shooter, I'm going to put it in the
translation, I'm hoping I can
translate this immediately so I don't
forget everything, so in my free time
I'm going to try to give you a translation
in a few months  There's a big problem with
Sanskrit. Sanskrit is
available, but it's corrupted because it was
handwritten.
There's a lot of help from Beijing. There are some very
good ones.
The chubby guy who's helping us, what's his name?
Stable Sur Sui?
Well, I don't know who he is, but if you know him,
I'm using his book because his
writings are... well, perfect. But it's okay. Okay,
script and Jamapa,
if it's possible to confuse someone in
just ten minutes. Okay, so that's my
goal this morning. We only have 15 minutes,
and it's special for me to know if it's possible to
confuse someone with the chicken in
just 10 minutes. Let's try it. Are you
ready? Put on your seatbelts.
[Music]
And so we finished the investigation
without the elements, and we chose the space
first.
And it goes to the end of the chapter.
Mix, who is one of our translators
from our special team of
translators called Pure Gold, you don't
know about this thing, but at the end
of the chapter he says, "
What space are you talking about? You're
both wrong." At the end of the
chapter he says, "I don't care what
space you're talking about. We'll talk about it. You're
both wrong." So if you don't
know about Buddhist philosophy,
which is talking about different
ideas...  of the element of space in
life in the school of life weapons and in
the second school which is the
centrist school the two lower schools
the text of this levitate javi give me the
first school the lower school is
better than any of us
and we already know that so the first
schools have a certain definition of
space in the second schools has
a slightly different explanation of
space and both keep careful in
the way the high school understands it
than the school of change the mediate
so we have to talk about what
the difference is between these two types of
spaces and so we can finish the
chapter and we can be more confused
than the next capital of baden action
by the way the next chapter is
called desire and attachment an investigation
of desire and prayer finistère
we must determine the chapter of the middle
of the elements first so there are two
types of space in Buddhism the
first
space does something fire like fire like
water like wind like
earth like
coal and oxygen
like gravity and does something and already has
a job does some house
someone wants abdominal because 20
dollars
has a
desperate end of that before you
answer  I'm going to help you have a
night. What functions does space have?
What does space do? I'm not looking in the
lowest school. It's
the space where objects exist, where
objects are held, and you can say, "That can be it."
Water makes things
flow, fire burns things, and space
is like the kind of place setting in a restaurant.
The head waiter in the restaurant
made a place for you. These three...
space is that.
[Music]
Here,
space is like the kind of place setting in a
restaurant where they kick out the other customers
after they leave their tip. I
have an empty chair for you. You can
stand here. Space has a function.
Space does something. It makes sense
because the other four elements are
famous for causing everything, everything physical. And
we talked about this in Chapter 3:
the elements in your body.
The four elements have a job.
Your body... So it makes sense that like
a club with four people there who
do everything, something gets done. So if a
fifth member joins, well, they also have to
do something, unless they're
the directors of the
Diamond Mountain board. He
joked,
and a new person joins the team, they
have to do something, right? They have to
do something.
So that's who said that.
The next school alarms, the school, its
sad says no, no, no,
space. Space has a job
here, but it's negative, the negative, and
just Justin is alive. It just doesn't stop
people from going there, and after that, it doesn't
stop Yuri's class, and it doesn't do anything about
the nightclub. And there's someone at
school who, if people in line, if
people get really drunk, well, you take them out
like you do, from that, well, only from the
movies,
someone has to take the other out of the
chair, and that's not a, but it doesn't do anything so you have
chairs in
space.
Space doesn't think about doing anything.
Space is just an absence of
anything. Space is an
absence of any quotients.
Let's take this book, which you're going to
buy. I'm telling you, it's sad. Let's
take this book as a physical object.
The job of space is just not to
block it.
The second school, the second school,
physical space, and physical space. This
book in space, space is just
there. It's in the absence of. It's almost something
physical. Okay, Hundred Dollar Garden,
the human dictionary is trying to
be calm.
We already talked about the space of the weapon that
does something with the definitions,
and  What is it that you are getting
that definition
time of the definition that is the
space of being defined or the definition
that already ends it that is how we beat
the guys of forget me now for 100
dollars that how we avoid the pse how
we defeat the ses to the limits how we
defeat the guys of the
second group of the percent more
pizza existing
if it is an association but that is not
the answer
that is the answer you are looking for
how we beat the how we defeat the
idea of ​​the Atlantic of space
space is the absence of something floor clothes
as the most difficult
the argument about the eye and the object
of the eye is very similar it
is very sophisticated and wrong
and then I have to sell them that
sell them the book the
book does not come from its own side
of the book cannot come from its
own anything
and we talked about that before we had already
talked about that but they forgot it
really is bad
we are at the end of chapter 5 where
was the what was
chapter 5 about
if the elements we were talking about
space and if you can do it you can
guess what he is going to say which is to see if
you can
who can fill for the  $0 in
the money to end
the last thing he's going to say let's go
Paraguay space
innovative orchard estuary next ahead
is the last thing are a zinc sandwich
class
is a good
$70 for a perfect answer
already Sunday for us elements
something interesting
that part when commenting in fact not even the
hand is lost we are in mystic
someone made a mistake when they carved it
with they made the manuscript is that
we have to find other copies
who is doing is awards there is
already a problem there is a big problem
with the manuscript something is missing is this
that part is lost
we found part unroll part in
Beijing another part
nothing only this we are missing some parts
and so we have to find them
we have to try to find the most
copies more copies
Jamie Mongolia find one in Mongolia
and french fries
yes it is very interesting that something is missing
some missing lines in that
comment and they will learn it as they
become translators
later the verses of Nagarjuna in his
comment in the comments of Chonis
Lamar and Stacey do better here they make
some mistakes and that is part of the art
is like it is
the wrong lines of the
translations a little different than  In
ancient times,
five people tried to translate "
water" as it was popular and usually the
best, but it's not always like the
English translations.
Amber is
in the right place,
but with a different translation, and that was
one of the translations that didn't
survive.
'We were carved 100, 500, or
600 years ago, and then they died, they
disappeared because the one that's around
was already very popular, but sometimes it's missing.
We have different ones.
Sometimes the
part of the carving of the way was
good, and the part of the old one was
good, but that's more work for
Michael because here, this is the
case: I have to compare the Sanskrit. There are
like five or six versions that come out, and
then I have to check the guy who did it, who
put it in yesterday's comments,
and we know it's someone else because
you realize that the teacher used a
different translation.
So these are problems for me,
for my life. You don't care,
and then there's my life more
miserable.
And what Aldo said is correct. There's a
part that's missing about "fresquito" that
first doesn't talk about
the four elements that can
affect your physical body.  And your eyes, your
ears, I would donate later. I'll talk about
space
in the second school. It's something that doesn't
change, something that isn't produced in the
absence of water. There, something happens.
Many moments with my teacher for 30
months. I'm sitting with many guys whose
freedom wasn't a little better than
mine. It's a thousand times better than mine, and I
hate it. I still hate it, but I try not to
talk about it. The
best answers in class. I
hated him. He
interrupted, and I said, "You see, he
interrupts, loves me,
and he said, 'I just thought of something,' and he said that
all the things that don't change are
negative, or I don't know, anxieties, and all the
things that don't change in the absence of
something in me, girls, and Rinko, who stayed, '
You know you're right.' And then I
was super jealous,
still super jealous, but I try, I try
to be okay,
and if you have a chance to study
with him once, his name is Art and
Gold. I hate to say his name, but he
taught me a lot. He's a great teacher,
New York, and they're in New York.
[Music]
I'm free in any way.
We cover the things that change
environments, like fire, earth,
water, and those molecules."  Molecules
are doing physical things, and that's the
definition of changing things because my
hair falls silent,
so changing wrinkles, salts in
Arizona, we get these spots,
and space,
remember the second school, is just an
absence of something, that's not changing, it doesn't
change because it doesn't ask about $100,
not
what to do,
Endesa, Hess, with this end of days
because its emptiness doesn't change, the vacuum or
not to the vacuum of dollars,
if it changes a little,
if the absence of European management of
exchange, a little bit with tension, something,
a little bit of clock would show, and there it's not
missing in this room,
that's changing or not changing,
100% changing, there's one, it's missing in this
room, it
can vary, it can become more, he commented
because if it changes 1%, you would have 1% of
elephant here in the room, and it's
im  It's possible the absence is always 5%
absences.
An old monk was asking if
an elephant only puts its nose in but its
body is outside the nose, then it's
no longer emptiness.
Yes, yes, although I'm not talking about
that. The emptiness of the mind elephant.
Rooms are changeable because if it changes
1%, then the elephant's nose
would appear here because 1% of the elephant
would appear here. You understand, an answer
to 75 questions, and this is part of the
missing page in the manuscript, and it
should be there, and it would be fun to
write them down, and we can't find it. The
page
about the things that are in between, those
things in between, between
changeable things and unchangeable things, and
image things. So,
imaginary things that aren't really things.
You can imagine
a pink elephant in the room. It's
changeable, one that changes, and the pink elephant
exists. The pink elephant has a
maximum existence. That's the factor you
were thinking about five minutes ago, but you
were thinking about it a while ago. We're not thinking about a
pink elephant. And
now, if you're thinking about a pink elephant,
or you think about pink elephants all the
time, you're not thinking about pink elephants all
the time. Okay, we call them
imaginary things that aren't  Real, if you ca
n't say changeable or non-changeable,
then the guy tries to come, says okay,
are you ready before we move on to
chapter 6,
and we leave the accountants behind.
Since we move on to chapter 6,
another guy comes, okay,
chapter 3. This chapter 4, you're
talking about elements, asking for
changeable things. Now, chapter 5, you talk about
space, non-changeable things, but I think there's
a real nature to
the imaginary things
of H&M.
The idea is, keep your mind, it's something
changeable, but I'm talking about the
elephant, not the thought about the
elephant. I'm talking about the
imaginary elephant. Can he carry
two trees?
And then you start debating about
that, but the comment is lost, you're going to have to
wait. Someone
should describe it to you,
although not very well. Now,
master, one
last thing:
at the end of many chapters,
a chain insults the others. Not
really because they're Buddhists, not
really insulting them, but not doing something
like,
before saying goodbye in
chapter 6, he's always going to say something like, ha ha ha, I'm
saying to her and her daughter what they
were watching. Quite naughty for me,
Tampa Bay, on hand.  of a passion for
this passion
and he says it's
the Tibetan was tempted
Washington
from Sanskrit in his task he
climbs to the par bochy to the bread to the bread
meaning very very small something very very very
small as he wants
coming out little monkey little monkey
a little little monkey little by little txiki little little
monkey little
and this is not going to be forgotten then alpha
means small Sanskrit but we are
more interested in the one you have to
know is wood and say buti buti you know
what it means [ __ ] gusta means [ __ ]
but the root
means to understand b and d h means to
understand me then doubt means the
person who understands everything who knows everything
and the word that I grabbed a usa here
is al pub bochy if you don't vote it means
mind your mind there are
many words in Sanskrit for
mind
you who are 'the for you
who have a small and
select small intellect a small brain so he
calls them and says the small brain
funny in Sanskrit if you can
learn all these special insults
from the ancient small books of the
small brain
if you think that things exist and
that  Things have to exist or not
exist, you think in your small brain
and to the popu guys, to the barguti, you who
believe that things have to exist or
not exist, you don't know how to stay in
the middle and you believe that to exist can't exist, you can't
find the way, it gave
me, you're not a small brain driving a
minivan and you're crashing into everything, it's
unhappy, you have an unhappy life, it's
crashing into everything, my small brain.
[Music]
What does it mean for 100 dollars
I want to give 100 dollars, you ca
n't answer twice in the
same morning, okay, ward
the users, she and she can answer,
so now I want to know if someone
says, come on, if something doesn't exist, the only
other option, if something is non-existent and a,
in fact, is the only other option is that it is
non-existent, web from my, which
means mini management, which castrated, I
had a minute, minivan, my level, you, my
level of a small brain, in existing
or non-existent, and you lost the way,
middle
or fiber is connected,
if you say that people are existing, they are
existing and you crash with that
thought, it means that you are thinking
that things exist on their own side,
and if you say that  You crash on the other side,
you say they no longer exist at all, they
have no stock, very good, 120
dollars,
and
from here you let yourself be seen, and if you let come,
Bieling is going to be indications, Lalín
9,
the one that follows, who is the existing one and
who are not, the existing ones, non-existent ones,
the husband of, I didn't do anything,
and the one who exists,
yes,
calmly, topic, and husband, help,
and 120, of an answer of 120 dollars
to 140 dollars, which is very good, very good
answer, it's a small brain, a small-
brained person, pieces that
things have to exist or not exist,
chapter 5 is closing
with its first controller in the middle, the
east, like, hahaha, excuse
me, but that's my nature,
now the last line of this chapter
is very beautiful
and not even for blocks, anyone who
sees things that way will never
have, nor urban,
in the same way, anyone who goes to
things that way will not have, nor will they,
he is playing, he is playing until
chapter 3 because in chapter 3
we discussed
seeing with your eyes,
closing his section of the counters of
three chapters and his last words
for the  Accountants, do
n't think that the kitchen mess
exists the way you thought and it hasn't
arrived today, it doesn't exist, there's no husband
in the kitchen,
don't make those two mistakes, stay in the
middle way, and then he says if you
keep seeing the husband the way you
see everything, he's angry
because he had a bad day, because he has to, because I
drive a lot, if you keep blaming
these incorrect reasons,
seeing it like that, you'll never see
Wang,
and what's the definition of my sister, they don't tire me out, they
drive, and I'm going to
give her some money, more
guts,
then permanent action,
that permanent feeling of
mental friction, because of the personal analysis, she
already has 30 dollars,
Austria, welcome to Austria,
it's good to see you,
and you have to give
Berlin program because I can't do two, I
have to go shopping,
but they're so united, alone with others, I
told them not to fight with me
[Music]
that way, those things, but he, but
seeing is a joke because in chapter 3
the beginning of the fight with the
accountants and more about seeing, and now
closes the chapter of the accountants  345
tells them that you'll never see
my brother's definition
is that if you understand
the accountants that the accountants are
wrong,
that you can stop your
negative emotions forever, said zio before and you
understand that the accountants are
wrong, being able to stop your
negative emotions forever, as a team, have
if you keep seeing things and you keep
indec, it's inefficient, you
keep thinking that the husband, seeing the
husband, will never know, nor will they go to a
destination, that there will be an urban definition, you
lose your desire, you lose your hate, you lose
your desire and you lose your power,
guess what the next chapter is and we're
going to investigate desire, that's a
good way to connect the chapters,
chapter 5 is very good accountants, I'm done
with you, but I'll just
tell you one thing, it's more, if you keep seeing
your husband in the kitchen the way you've been
seeing him, then you
were looking to know nirvana, and then it goes to the
next chapter, which is the next
chapter, infrastructure, desire research, desire
research